Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
- United Textile Workers of America, Publication (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New Bedford Strike!, 1928; Publication (Box 387, Folder 4)
    Author: New Bedford Textile Council
  - Item 2: New Bedford workers, 27,000 strong have said an emphatic 'no' to the organized manufacturers' attempt to make a 10 per cent wage cut, 1928; Publication (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Correspondence - The New Bedford Textile strike has entered into its eighteenth week., 1928; Publication (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Truth about the Lawrence Police, 1919; Publication (Box 387, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 3 (Feb., Apr. 1919)
  - Item 5: Lawrence: a strike for wages or for Bolshevism?, 1919; Publication (Box 387, Folder 4)
    Author: John A. Fitch
- United Textile Workers of America, Publication (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Effect of the Taft-Hartley Law on the workers in specific Southern Textile Mills, chronology and summary, 1953; Publication (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Winning better conditions with the CIO, Publication (Box 387, Folder 5)
    Notes: Article. Second copy
  - Item 3: Correspondence - The purpose of this letter is to acquaint you with an important issue that has reached a climax, 1946; Publication (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Program for the Eighth Biennial Convention of the, 1944; Publication (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Summary of statement of Joseph Jacobs, Southern Director and Southern General Counsel of Atlanta, GA, United Textile Workers of America, AFL, before the Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1953; Publication (Box 387, Folder 5)
    Author: Joseph Jacobs
- NFTW (National Federation of Telephone Workers), Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Statement with respect to referendum provisions of the Constitution of the CWA (Communications Workers of America), 1947; Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: An analysis of the proposed organization and financial structure of the CWA (Communications Workers of America), 1947; Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Rules of the Telephone Workers Organizing, Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The CIO or AFL - which shall it be for Telephone Workers?, 1947; Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Correspondence - In accordance with our recent discussions, the Congress of Industrial Organizations hereby constitutes and appoints the following group as the Telephone Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: What is wrong with, 1947; Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Communication destroys isolation, Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
    Notes: Flyer.
  - Item 8: Correspondence - Thank you for your letter of Dec. 18. It is gratifying to know of your interest in our organization, 1948; Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
    Author: Telephone Workers Organizing Committee
  - Item 9: Telephone organizer, 1948-1949 (Box 387, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.4-12; v.2;no.1-2, 4-6
  - Item 10: NJ Bell finds 12 more cables cut in walkout, 1950-1953 (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Strike cuts Jersey phone service, 1950-1953 (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Phone union wins pay rise in Jersey, 1950-1953 (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Jersey phone union signs new contract, 1950-1953 (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Affiliation for telegraph workers, Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Effect of the Taft-Hartley Law on workers in textile mills, 1953; Publication (Box 387, Folder 6)
- United Textile Workers of America, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Open Shop Bulletin, no. 14, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: NAM (National Association of Manufacturers)
  - Item 2: Minutes of the Support the Passaic Strike Conference - June 25, 1926, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: General Relief Committee Textile Strikers, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Workers Union or Bosses' Union?, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: to Robert Dunn - Re: copy of your report, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Relief Bulletin, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Passaic Textile Strikers
    Notes: v.1:no.2
  - Item 7: A strike and an American, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Oswald Garrison Villard
  - Item 8: Statement by Albert Weisbord; Statement by Charles M. Joseph, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Albert Weisbord; Charles M. Joseph
  - Item 9: Correspondence - You realize that strikes mean suffering, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Emergency Committee for Strikers' Relief
  - Item 10: The Passaic Strike, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Minutes - Oct. 18, 1926, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: American Civil Liberties Union
  - Item 12: Correspondence - And now the Textile bosses have trotted out the usual bomb, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Passaic Textile Strikers Relief Campaign
  - Item 13: Correspondence - Mary Heaton vorse, who so interestingly wrote about the Big Steel Strike, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: General Relief Committee, Textile Strikers
  - Item 14: correspondence - 20,000 strikers and their sympathizers paraded yesterday in Passaic, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Support the Passaic Strike, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Account of meeting of John Sherman, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: The Arbitrator, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.5
  - Item 18: Beauty and the beast at Passaic, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Louis Budenz
  - Item 19: The Passaic Textile Workers Strike, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Ben Gitlow
  - Item 20: Women of Passaic, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Winifred L. Chappell
  - Item 21: Russia's Dark Heritage, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: John R. Voris
  - Item 22: B of R C student dramatizes big textile strike, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: The Passaic Textile Strike, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Gilbert Page Simmons
  - Item 24: Minutes of Executive Committee for NYC Conference - General Relief Committee Textile Strikers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: At the Conference on Relief for Passaic, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: League for Industrial Democracy
  - Item 26: Statement of W. Jett Lauck, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: W. Jett Lauck
  - Item 27: Story of the Strike - the textile industry, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Coffin Society - Atterbury's idea of union, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: Brookwood begins campaign to bring workers to power meet, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: The War in Passaic, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Mary Heaton Vorse
  - Item 31: The Democrats stand by Mellon, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Frank R. Kent
  - Item 32: At the Passaic Battlefront, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Ernest W. Mandeville
  - Item 33: An old-fashioned strike, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
    Author: Beulah Amidon
  - Item 34: News pictures for newspapers!, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Congressional Record - Sixty-ninth Congress, First Session, Publication (Box 388, Folder 1)
- Botany Consolidated Mills, Publication (Box 388, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Railway Clerk, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.25:no.4
  - Item 2: The Nation, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.122:no.3173
  - Item 3: correspondence - I regret very much to find that by oversight your letter of Apr 20th has not yet been answered, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 2)
    Author: Botany Consolidated Mills
  - Item 4: Hell in New Jersey: story of the Passaic Textile Strike, told in pictures, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 2)
- Textile Strike Bulletin, Publication (Box 388, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Textile Strike Bulletin - v.1, no. 1-2, 4-25 (1926), Publication (Box 388, Folder 3)
- Passaic Daily Herald, Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Botany says 'no need for conferences', 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
    Notes: Passaic Daily Herald news clippings
  - Item 2: Sheriff removes men brought in for strike duty, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Vote unanimously for leadership of Albert Weisbord, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Strike leader to let Unitd Front men act..., 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Strikers vote Weisbord full power, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Hopeful outlook and plans to see Mill owners...., 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Governor Moor warns Kiwanians of Communism, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Strikers will test riot act..., 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Strikers flock to Garfield to watch arrests, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Weisbord talks to strikers at Clifton Church, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Injunction prevents Sheriff Nimmo and his men from interfering, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Strikers hold Garfield meeting, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Court over-rules Nimmo's bockade of Belmont Park, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Second battle of Passaic!, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Strikers accept, graphic offer of mediation, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: 8 strikers arrested - 2 jailed for 30 days, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Strikers accept graphics offer to bring peace in textile strife, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Refuse leniency to textile strikers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Strikers may defy order on picketing, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Textile Barons fail to destroy workers unity, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Bosses weaken while workers grow stronger, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Police arrest Botany Mill picket leader, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Passaic strikers routed by fire hose as gas bombs fail, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Strikers refuse to fail into arbitration trap set by the Mayor and others in Passaic, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Clifton Police brutally beat strike pickets, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: Striker given thirty-day term, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: More pickets arrested at Textile mill, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 28: Daily workers reporter arrested, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 29: Polict terrorize strikers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 30: 25,000 more mill workers ready to strike, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 31: Jersey strike spreading, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 32: Warrant issued for Passaic Police on assault charge, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 33: Walkout of 25,000 more predicted as protest over Police clubbings, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 34: Warrants out for Police as clubbers in Mill strike, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 35: Can't get anybody to arrest Police, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 36: Passaic Police Chief is ordered arrested for strike clubbing, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: Mills reject wise as strike mediator, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 38: Passaic strikers demonstrate joy with big parade, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 39: Moore seeks truth in Mill strike, Civic bodies hail plan for peace, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 40: Mary Heaton Vorse writes on valiant mother in strike, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 41: Strikers and children march in Washington, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 42: Passaic to adopt riot tactics today, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 43: Mayor Burke did not have sheriff read riot act, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 44: Writ of Habeas Corpus for Weisbord granted, Sheriff may not send his men here, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 45: Sheriff Morgan decides not to send his deputies here now, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 46: Strikers and children leave for Washington ..., 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 47: Garfield striker, found dead in bed, died of natural causes, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 48: Mill strike tots picket as town curbs 'riot act', 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 49: Test meeting in Garfield is dispersed, Dr. Thomas is jailed, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 50: Armstrong nearly at blows with Wallisch, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 51: Strikers death not due to any Police clubbing, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 52: Weisbord out Saturday to appeal for liberty, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 53: Justic Black to decide upon writ of habeas corpus, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 54: Borah may try to mediate, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 55: Wool workers' thrift, mill wages and men's savings, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 56: Premier Mussolini sees no international crisis breeding war, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 57: Weisbord agrees to step aside in negotiations looking to peace, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 58: News of teh City of Garfield, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 59: Gusciora found by grapplers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 60: Citizens Committee is taken sharply to task for its stand, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 61: $3,000 blaze forces people into streets during drizzling rain, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 62: Masked Ban shoots down 2 Garfield women, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 63: State Dept. of Health states Passaic stats, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 64: Passaic $3,000 a year Police dictator, once poor, now lives in $70,000 mansion, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 65: Strikers to stop picketing F & H, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 66: Borah plans to discuss strike before Senate, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 67: Injunction orders strikers to stop picketing F&H, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 68: Senator Edwards vigorously opposes LaFollette resolution, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 69: Deplores strikers' skill in putting cities on defensive, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 70: Wool Council man swears blacklist has been kept up, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 71: Strikers must stay away from F&H Mills, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 72: Singing woman leads 2,500 strikers in March, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 73: Mayor Passaic to hear strikers ..., 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 74: Police attacks end as textile strikers Don Steel Helmets, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 75: Police in sidecars club and chase 3,000 in Passaic Strike, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 76: Textile strikers defy Police order, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 77: Strike leaders score Police, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 78: 600 Strike pickets clash with Police, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 79: Riots feared as strikersMill workers defiant as cops use clubs again, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 80: Pickets serenade Jersey dye plant, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 81: Will ask Coolidge for textile inquiry, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 82: Mill owners agree to Davis mediation, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 83: Coolidge to hear Mill Strikers' plea, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 84: Passaic leader says this will be biggest textile walk-out the country has seen, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 85: Picket leader defies Sheriff and is arrested while insisting on his rights, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 86: Mill strikers veto US mediation plan, demand $50 a week, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 87: Mr. Seger defends Passaic's good name in speech to house, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 88: Use clubs, horses and motorcycles to clear sidewalks - 14 arrests, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 89: Police swing clubs on textile strikers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 90: Strikers clubbed denounce..., 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 91: Passaic Police ride down strikers in renewed reign of terror, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 92: Mill strike inquiry asked by Senator, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 93: Employes to get Military training, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 94: Espionage code given detectives by employers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 95: Spies aggravate Passaic strikers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 96: Strike disorders denied by Seger, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 97: Passaic Priest hits at strike leaders, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 98: Textile strikers again ask inquiry, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 99: Policemen fight textile strikers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 100: Passaic textile strike shows industry's needs, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 101: Strikers call upon Edwards, Senatorial hearing delayed, Hilfers comments on offer, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 102: Assurances given of appropriation for deeper river, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 103: Four year term for Clifton and Garfield Mayors, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 104: The Botany Mills cut many melons, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 105: Moore signs picket bill, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 106: Seek the arrest of Passaic Chief, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 107: Federation rejects plea of Weisbord, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 108: Says strike impends in Lawrence Mills, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 109: Passaic strike laid to national unrest, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 110: Plan public protest at baking merger, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 111: Botany Mills have profit of $992,983, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 112: Strike leader's chauffeur loses driving license, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 113: Strikers entertained by Senator Edwards at his home last night, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 114: Woman striker is fined $50 for throwing pepper, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 115: Senator Edwards talks to strikers at his own home, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 116: Police and strikers battle at Passaic, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 117: Mills to take back few strikers only, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 118: Children to march in Passaic strike, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 119: Strike chief assails Botany Mills report, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 120: Six strikers arrested on refusal to disperse, Passaic police rout children's paradise, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 121: Plan to open passaic Mills arouses strikers, leader says it will be 'grand closing day', 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 122: Strikers flee as riot act is read, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 123: Move to mediate Passaic strike, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 124: ...Law as a menace to Liberty and Breede, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 125: Riot act and clubs rout 5,000 strikers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - Item 126: Cops club women, drag one to jail, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 4)
- Passaic Daily Herald, Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Passaic textile strike, 1927; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Passaic: the story of a struggle against starvation wages and for the right to organize, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
    Author: Albert Weisbord
  - Item 3: The Textile strike of 1926: Passaic, Clifton, Garfield, Lodi, New Jersey., Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Prisoners of the Passaic Strike, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
    Author: Hollace Ransdell
  - Item 5: Labor defender, Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The Christian Century: a journal of religion: the Passaic Strike, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Special Daily report by the Federated Press, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Union Labor Messenger - v.8, no. 89, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Abstract of address by Dr. Stephen S. Wise, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Supplementary statement of W. Jett Lauck, economist for Passaic Textile Strikers, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Nearly a thousand Workers arrested during the Passaic Textile Strike, 1926; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Bericht der Kammgarnspinnerei Stohr & Co.., 1925; Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
    Language: German.
  - Item 13: Hell in New Jersey: story of the Passaic Textile Strike, told in pictures, Publication (Box 388, Folder 5)
- Passaic Daily Herald, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Weisbord leaves union leadership as charter comes, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Lauck Committee to wind up its affairs very soon, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Wagenknecht still in charge of strikers relief, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Strike headquarters reports Weisbord is to take long rest, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Strikers' parade Sept. 11 to mark entry in AFL, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Leader for 32 weeks gets great reception when he leaves post, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Citizens' group makes attack on relief appeals, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The strike and the local press, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Discredits tale Weisbord is out, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Committee sees UT officers to ask charter, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Black hand threat sent to Weisbord, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Strike playground visited by group of Slavic leaders, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Slavic group's reply, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Workers' cause vested in independent Committee pending transfer to UTW Weisbord expelled by Communist Party?, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Mills think AFL will prolong stick, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Citizens to urge silk strike inquiry, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Chicago Headquarters sent instructions to "Pioneers" in Passaic, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: He finds former willing but latter holding off--citizens again show Communist tie-up, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: McMahon calls tax on textiles unjust, Publication (Box 388, Folder 6)